Guide to the Dance Pages Records,1930-1997, bulk 1982-1997
American Dance Festival Archives
Dance Pages records 1930-1997, bulk 1982-1997
American Dance Festival Archives
Dance Pages
5.0 linear feet
Dance Pages (circa 1983-1997), a quarterly magazine, presented its readers with articles about a wide range of dance genres, performances, companies, and individual dancers. The magazine also contained studio listings, book and video reviews, and information about dance history and health. Kenneth Romo and Donna Gianell, both professional dancers, created Dance Pages as a hobby, and they continued to serve as the publishers and editors of the magazine as it grew in size and scope. In 1995, the magazine changed names, becoming Dance & the Arts, and moved to a bimonthly publication schedule. The magazine dissolved around 1997. The collection includes publicity information, magazines, drafts of articles and advertisements, paste-ups for advertisements and magazine features, newspaper clippings, press kits, programs, flyers, brochures, catalogs, invoices, personal and professional correspondence, photographs, contact sheets, negatives, 35 mm slides, and transparencies.
ADF.004
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
The Dance Pages Records were received by the American Dance Festival Archives as a gift in 2013.
Historical Note
Dance Pages (circa 1983-1997), a quarterly magazine, presented its readers with articles about a wide range of dance genres, performances, companies, and individual dancers. The magazine also contained studio listings, book and video reviews, and information about dance history and health. Kenneth Romo and Donna Gianell, both professional dancers, created Dance Pages as a hobby, and they continued to serve as the publishers and editors of the magazine as it grew in size and scope. In 1995, the magazine changed names, becoming Dance & the Arts, and moved to a bimonthly publication schedule. The magazine dissolved around 1997.
The husband and wife team of Romo and Gianell originally conceived the magazine as a way to provide local and visiting dance students with comprehensive information about New York City teachers, dance studios, and schedules. In the mid-1980s, Dance Pages was incorporated and began to expand into the national market in both advertising and editorial coverage. Designed to appeal to a broad audience, the magazine published articles about a wide range of dance, including classical ballet, modern, tap, jazz, ballroom, and ethnic dance, as well as dance history. It also covered a variety of performance platforms for dance, such as concert, video, television, film, Broadway, and festivals. In addition, Dance Pages featured information about health, dance injury-related exercises, and conditioning and toning exercises. Book, video, and Broadway reviews also appeared in the magazine. Dance Pages, and later Dance & the Arts, continued to feature listings of both New York City and national studios.
Collection Overview
The collection contains the records of Dance Pages, which were collected or created during the production of the magazine, as well as copies of the magazine from 1987 to 1997. Records were typically filed by subject or person rather than by type of record, so files contain a range of materials. The majority of the Dance Pages records are subject files, which primarily contain publicity information such as photographs and press releases for dance companies, dancers, schools, teachers, artists, musicians, filmmakers, photographers, performance venues, events, performances, and other dance-related topics. In addition to publicity materials, subject folders can contain drafts of articles and advertisements, paste-ups for advertisements and magazine features, illustrated graphics, press clippings, correspondence, invoices, brochures, flyers, programs, 35 mm slides, and negatives. The collection also contains administrative files, which hold materials related to magazine contributors, personnel, and business management. While the collection includes some financial documentation and correspondence, these materials are filed with the subject to which they pertain and are therefore distributed throughout the collection.
The materials housed within the collection are in a variety of formats, including paper-based records, magazines, paste-ups, illustrated graphics, newspaper clippings, press kits, programs, flyers, brochures, and catalogs, as well as photographs, contact sheets, negatives, 35 mm slides, and transparencies.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged into three series: Magazines, Subject Files, and Administrative Files.
Subject Headings
Gianell, Donna; Romo, Kenneth; Dance Pages, Inc.; Dance Pages.; Dance & the Arts.; Dance -- Periodicals; Fine Arts; Performing Arts -- Dance
Detailed Description of Collection
- Magazines, 1987-1997, (13 folders)
  Arranged chronologically.
  The Magazines series contains copies of Dance Pages magazine, beginning with Spring 1987 (vol. 5, no. 1) and ending with September/October 1997 (vol. 15, no. 2). Two issues from 1987 (vol. 5, no. 2-3) and issues published before 1987 are not included in the collection.
  - Spring, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Fall, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Winter/Spring, Spring/Summer, Summer, Fall, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Winter, Spring, Summer, September/October, November/December, 1995 (Box 1)
  - January/February, March/April, May/June, 1996 (Box 1)
  - July/August, September/October, November/December, 1996 (Box 1)
  - January/February, March/April, May/June, 1997 (Box 1)
  - July/August, September/October, 1997 (Box 1)
- Subject Files, 1930-1997, undated, (3 boxes; 515 folders)
  The Subject Files series is divided into seven subseries.
  - Dance and Arts Associations, 1983-1995, undated, 6 folders
    Arranged alphabetically.
    The Dance and Arts Associations subseries contains press releases, newsletters, reports, brochures, programs, correspondence, and a press information packet.
    - Center for Arts Information, 1983, undated (Box 1)
    - Dance/USA Annual Report and Three Year Plan, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Dance World Press Information Packet, 1995 (Box 1)
    - International Contortion Society, 1984 (Box 1)
    - International Tap Association, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts National Dance Residency Program Grants, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Dance Companies and Dancers, 1930-1997, undated, 432 folders
    Arranged alphabetically. One folder containing unidentified photographs is filed under "unidentified."
    The majority of the materials in the Dance Companies and Dancers subseries are publicity photographs and press releases. Other materials include drafts of articles, advertisement copy, paste-ups, press clippings, resumes, correspondence, invoices, brochures, flyers, programs, contact sheets, 35 mm slides, and negatives. All folders in the subseries contain photographs, with the exception of Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre, Gary Duncan, ISO, Belinda James, Sankai Juku, Diane Latchrupp and Paul Pellicorno, Sun Ock Lee, Neryda, and Newark Dance Theatre.
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre, 1994 (Box 1)
    - B. Muse, Inc. Dance Theatre, undated (Box 1)
    - Hikari Baba Dancers, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Bailos La Compania De Baile, Inc., undated (Box 1)
    - Balinese American Dance Theatre, 1982-1983, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet Austin, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet British Columbia, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Ballet Concierto de Puerto Rico, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet de Monterrey, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet du Nord, 1987, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet Espanol de Madrid, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet Florida, 1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet Royale Academy, undated (Box 1)
    - Ballet Theatre International, undated (Box 1)
    - Les Ballets Africains, undated (Box 1)
    - Lygya Barreto, 1996, undated (Box 1)
    - Bavarian National Ballet, 1992-1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Nanette Bearden, Renaissance Awards, undated (Box 1)
    - Nanette Bearden Contemporary Dance Theatre, undated (Box 1)
    - Talley Beatty, Renaissance Awards, undated (Box 1)
    - Beijing Opera, undated (Box 1)
    - Sue Bernhard Dance Works, undated (Box 1)
    - Big Dance, undated (Box 1)
    - Big Dance Theater, undated (Box 1)
    - Richard Biles Dance Company, undated (Box 1)
    - Mary Bruce Blackburn, 1993, undated (Box 1)
    - The Blanco Dances, undated (Box 1)
    - Beppie Blankert, undated (Box 1)
    - Bolshoi Ballet, 1986-1996, undated (Box 1)
    - Boston Ballet, 1995, undated (Box 1)
    - The Boston Conservatory, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Freddick Bratcher and Company, undated (Box 1)
    - The Brooklyn Dance Theater, undated (Box 1)
    - Trisha Brown Company, 1989-1991, undated (Box 1)
    - Burklyn Ballet Theatre, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Butler Ballet, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Donald Byrd/The Group, 1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Chandralekha and Deepti Gupta, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Tony Charmoli, undated (Box 1)
    - Nai-Ni Chen, 1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Kiken Chin, undated (Box 1)
    - Yoshiko Chuma, 1987, undated (Box 1)
    - Martha Clarke, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Elinor Coleman, 1987, undated (Box 1)
    - Kitty Collins, undated (Box 1)
    - Steve Condos, 1990, undated (Box 1)
    - Collin Connor, 1992-1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Robert Rene Contreras, undated (Box 1)
    - Charles Cook, 1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Ilona Copen, 1988, undated (Box 1)
    - Creach/Koester, 1983-1984, undated (Box 1)
    - Nadia Creamer, undated (Box 1)
    - Pamela Critelli, undated (Box 1)
    - Blondell Cummings, undated (Box 1)
    - Merce Cunningham, 1973, 1983, undated (Box 1)
    - John Curry, undated (Box 1)
    - Dalia: Dances of Passion, undated (Box 1)
    - Christopher D'Amboise, undated (Box 1)
    - Jacques D'Amboise, 1994-1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Starr Danias, undated (Box 1)
    - Eleanor D'Antuono, 1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Mickey Davidson, 1997, undated (Box 1)
    - Pam De Fina, undated (Box 1)
    - Carmen De Lavallade, undated (Box 1)
    - Kyle deCamp, undated (Box 1)
    - Andrea Del Conte, 1993-1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Nikki Della Penta, undated (Box 1)
    - Denishawn Repertory Dancers, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Deva Deva, undated (Box 1)
    - Djoniba, 1989-1995, undated (Box 1)
    - Maura Nguyen Donohue, undated (Box 1)
    - Pierre Dulaine and Yvonne Marceau, undated (Box 1)
    - Gary Duncan - Dance Alive, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Kenn Duncan, undated (Box 1)
    - Maria Durante, 1985-1992, undated (Box 1)
    - Ilya Gaft, 1960-1962, 1991-1992, undated (Box 2)
    - Annabelle Gamson, 1985-1986, undated (Box 2)
    - Fred Garbo, undated (Box 2)
    - Keely Garfield, undated (Box 2)
    - Brian Gary, undated (Box 2)
    - Janie Geiser, undated (Box 2)
    - Margie Gillis, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Lisa Giobbi, 1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Tiye Giraud, undated (Box 2)
    - Savion Glover, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Claude Godin, undated (Box 2)
    - Jim Gold, undated (Box 2)
    - Linda Gold, undated (Box 2)
    - Rob Goldwitz, undated (Box 2)
    - Marcelo Gomez, undated (Box 2)
    - Annabella Gonzalez, 1982-1985, undated (Box 2)
    - Ain Gordon and David Gordon, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Jean Gordon, undated (Box 2)
    - Martita Goshen, undated (Box 2)
    - Martha Graham, 1938, 1943, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Katherine Gramer, undated (Box 2)
    - Harriette Ann Gray, undated (Box 2)
    - Jose Greco, Jose Greco II, undated (Box 2)
    - Renato Greco, 1989, undated (Box 2)
    - Allyson Green, undated (Box 2)
    - Neil Greenberg, undated (Box 2)
    - David Greenspan, undated (Box 2)
    - Cynthia Gregory, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Billy Grey and Kelly Carrol, 1989-1991, undated (Box 2)
    - Daryl Grey, undated (Box 2)
    - Lance Gries, undated (Box 2)
    - Katherine Griffith, 1990 (Box 2)
    - Yuri Grigorovich, undated (Box 2)
    - Maximiliano Guerra, undated (Box 2)
    - Rick Guimond, undated (Box 2)
    - Blanca Gutierrez, 1986, undated (Box 2)
    - H. T. Chen and Dancers, undated (Box 2)
    - Joe Hall Dancers, 1989, undated (Box 2)
    - The Hanover Children's Ballet Theatre and Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Rachel Harms Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Hartford Ballet, 1982, 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Hawaii State Ballet, undated (Box 2)
    - Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1981-1986, undated (Box 2)
    - Hoctor's Dance Caravan, undated (Box 2)
    - Joseph Holmes Dance Theater, 1986-1989, undated (Box 2)
    - Houston Ballet, undated (Box 2)
    - Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, 1989-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Hungarian State Folk Ensemble, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Ice Theatre of New York, 1986-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Saeko Ichinohe, undated (Box 2)
    - David Ilku, undated (Box 2)
    - Impulse Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - In Forward Motion, undated (Box 2)
    - Inbal Co., circa 1970 (Box 2)
    - Indianapolis Ballet Theatre, 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Indrani, undated (Box 2)
    - Infinity Dance Theater, 1995-1997, undated (Box 2)
    - Bill Irwin, undated (Box 2)
    - ISO, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Sachiyo Ito and Company, 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - J. Fregalette Jansen Dance, undated (Box 2)
    - Janet Jackson, 1989-1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Melinda Jackson, undated (Box 2)
    - Curt Jacobs, undated (Box 2)
    - Susan Jacobson, undated (Box 2)
    - Susan Jaffe, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Adam James, undated (Box 2)
    - Belinda James, undated (Box 2)
    - Randy James, undated (Box 2)
    - Judith Jamison, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Heather Janise, undated (Box 2)
    - Andrew Jannetti, undated (Box 2)
    - Denise Jefferson, undated (Box 2)
    - Finis Jhung, undated (Box 2)
    - The Joffrey Ballet, undated (Box 2)
    - Christina Johnson, undated (Box 2)
    - Alan Jones, 1989, undated (Box 2)
    - Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zanes Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Raul Juarena/New York-Buenos Aires Connection, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Sankai Juku, undated (Box 2)
    - Lenny Juliano, undated (Box 2)
    - Dorothy Jungels/Everett Dance Theater, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Roxanne D'Orleans Juste, undated (Box 2)
    - K2 Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Yamabushi Kagura, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Kamizawa Modern Dance Ensemble, undated (Box 2)
    - Kathy's Cable Kids, undated (Box 2)
    - Jerry Kaufman, 1987, undated (Box 2)
    - Nora Kaye, undated (Box 2)
    - Pooh Kaye and the Eccentric Motions, undated (Box 2)
    - Sam Keany, undated (Box 2)
    - Kei Takei's Moving Earth, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Charles Kelley, undated (Box 2)
    - Gene Kelley, undated (Box 2)
    - Joy Kellman, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Eileen Kelly, undated (Box 2)
    - John Kelly, undated (Box 2)
    - Rebecca Kelly Dance Company, 1986-1996, undated (Box 2)
    - The Kennedy Dancers, undated (Box 2)
    - Konrad Kinard, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Elisa King and Dancers, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Katiti King, undated (Box 2)
    - Robert Kintz, undated (Box 2)
    - Gelsey Kirkland, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Kirov Ballet, undated (Box 2)
    - Billie Kirpich, undated (Box 2)
    - Andy Kirshner, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Darci Kistler, undated (Box 2)
    - Tommi Kitti, undated (Box 2)
    - Marilyn Klaus, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Jo Anna Kneeland, undated (Box 2)
    - Kofi Koko, 1984, undated (Box 2)
    - Irina Kolpakova, 1989, undated (Box 2)
    - Stephan Koplowitz and Company, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Valentina Kozlova, undated (Box 2)
    - Kremlin Ballet, undated (Box 2)
    - Ed Kresley, undated (Box 2)
    - Tomas Kubinek, 1996, undated (Box 2)
    - Kultur, undated (Box 2)
    - Dance Kumikokimoto, undated (Box 2)
    - Ellen Lacher, undated (Box 2)
    - Phyllis Lamhut Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Kiki Lammersen, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Eric Lamp, undated (Box 2)
    - Rachel Lampert, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Christy Lane, undated (Box 2)
    - Pearl Lang, undated (Box 2)
    - Lanonima Imperial, undated (Box 2)
    - Joe Lanteri, undated (Box 2)
    - Regina Larkin, undated (Box 2)
    - Diane Latchrupp and Paul Pellicorno, undated (Box 2)
    - Kathleen Laziza, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Cyndi Lee Dance Company, 1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Georgia Lee, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Janet Lee, 1982, undated (Box 2)
    - Sun Ock Lee, Zen Dance Technique, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Ballet Guild of the Lehigh Valley (PA), 1996 (Box 2)
    - Ralph Lemon, undated (Box 2)
    - Lawrence Leritz, 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - LeTang Tap Dance, undated (Box 2)
    - Jane Lewis, undated (Box 2)
    - DANCE June Lewis and Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Murray Lewis Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Gladys Liberatore, undated (Box 2)
    - Anna Liceica, undated (Box 2)
    - Andris Liepa, undated (Box 2)
    - Janet Lilly, undated (Box 2)
    - Jose Limon Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Hsiang-Hsiu Lin, undated (Box 2)
    - Michael Lineberry, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Wang Hai Ling, undated (Box 2)
    - June and Freda Lippel, 1990, undated (Box 2)
    - Rachel List and Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Dorothy D. Lister, undated (Box 2)
    - Valentina Litvinoff, undated (Box 2)
    - Lo Lan Dance Company, 1991, undated (Box 2)
    - Lesley J. Lockery, undated (Box 2)
    - Les Grands Ballets de Loony, undated (Box 2)
    - Lourdes Lopez, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Miguel Lopez, undated (Box 2)
    - Loudoun Ballet Company, undated (Box 2)
    - The Stanley Love Performance Group, undated (Box 2)
    - Steve Love, 1991-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Lar Lubovitch Dance Company, undated (Box 2)
    - Luigi, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Larry Lynd, undated (Box 2)
    - Evee Lynn, undated (Box 2)
    - Candy Lynne, undated (Box 2)
    - Carnell Lyons (90th Birthday Party), 1992 (Box 2)
    - Malashock Dance and Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Manhattan Tap, 1992, undated (Box 3)
    - Michael Mao Dance, 1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Susan Marshall Dance Company, 1993, undated (Box 3)
    - Cecilia Marta Dance Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Masashi and Action Machine, Nagoya, Japan, undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Mathieu Dance, 1986, undated (Box 3)
    - Matsuyama Ballet, 1991, undated (Box 3)
    - Shawn McConneloug and her Orchestra, undated (Box 3)
    - Gloria McLean, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Memphis Concert Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Mesopotamian Opera Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Metropolitan Opera, undated (Box 3)
    - Miami City Ballet, 1990-1991, undated (Box 3)
    - Bebe Miller and Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Milwaukee Ballet, 1992, undated (Box 3)
    - Mime Dance Theatre, undated (Box 3)
    - Momentum Dance Theater, undated (Box 3)
    - Monterrey Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Anthony Morgan Dance Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Moscow Festival Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Moulton Dance Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Mount Baker Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Daniel Nagrin, undated (Box 3)
    - Dennis Nahat, undated (Box 3)
    - Najwa Dance Corps, undated (Box 3)
    - Natsu Nakajima, undated (Box 3)
    - Namaste Danse, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Patricia N. Nanon, undated (Box 3)
    - Nashville Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - National Ballet of Canada, 1995, undated (Box 3)
    - National Ballet of Spain, undated (Box 3)
    - National Ballet of Washington (DC), 1964 (Box 3)
    - Nebula, undated (Box 3)
    - Nederlands Dans Theatre, 1984-1986, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Neo Labos Dancetheatre, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
    - Neryda, 1930, undated (Box 3)
    - Nevada Dance Theatre, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Phoebe Neville, undated (Box 3)
    - New Orleans Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - New York Baroque Dance Company, 1986-1991, undated (Box 3)
    - New York Theatre Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Newark Dance Theatre, 1987, undated (Box 3)
    - Rosalind Newman, undated (Box 3)
    - Nijinsky and Vaslav Nijinsky Medal, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Dilana Nikiforova, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Nikolais and Murray Louis Dance, Nikolais Dance Theatre, 1978-1995, undated (Box 3)
    - Pola Nirenska, undated (Box 3)
    - Nis Bundor Spiderwoman Theater, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Mikko Nissinen, undated (Box 3)
    - Noche Flamenca, undated (Box 3)
    - Rudolf Nureyev, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3)
    - NYU Washington Square Repertory Dance Company, 1995 (Box 3)
    - O Vertigo Danse, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Jody Oberfelder Dance Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Tere O'Connor Dance, undated (Box 3)
    - Compagnie Rick Odums/Paris, 1990, undated (Box 3)
    - Offspring Dance Company, 1989, undated (Box 3)
    - Open 24 Hours Dance Company, undated (Box 3)
    - Orlando City Ballet, undated (Box 3)
    - Wendy Osserman Dance Company, 1986, undated (Box 3)
    - Overfoot Dance Company, 1992, undated (Box 3)
    - Pacific Northwest Ballet, 1992-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Pacific Northwest Ballet, 1992-1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Hermes Pan, 1941-1942, undated (Box 3)
    - David Parker Dance Company, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Lynn Parkerson, undated (Box 3)
    - Claire Porter, undated (Box 3)
    - Premiere Dance, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Peter Pucci, undated (Box 3)
    - Evangeline Queroz, undated (Box 3)
    - Shantal Quincy, undated (Box 3)
    - Pam Quinn, undated (Box 3)
    - Kathy Lani Rae Rafko, undated (Box 3)
    - Kevin Ramsey, undated (Box 3)
    - Toshi Reagon, undated (Box 3)
    - Allison Reed, 1987, undated (Box 3)
    - Marc Reed, undated (Box 3)
    - Ann Reinking, undated (Box 3)
    - Judith Ren-Lay, undated (Box 3)
    - Johan Renuall, undated (Box 3)
    - Gary Restivo, undated (Box 3)
    - Nancy Reynolds, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Paolo Ribeiro, undated (Box 3)
    - Pollyana Ribeiro, undated (Box 3)
    - Desmond Richardson and Dwight Rhoden, undated (Box 3)
    - Lynn Rielly, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Scott Rink, 1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Pilar Rioja, undated (Box 3)
    - Carol Rioux, undated (Box 3)
    - Patricia Ripley, undated (Box 3)
    - Bimbo Rivas (Coco Bal), undated (Box 3)
    - Bob Rizzo, undated (Box 3)
    - Francis Roach, undated (Box 3)
    - Jana Robbins, undated (Box 3)
    - Davis Robertson, undated (Box 3)
    - Cathy Roe, undated (Box 3)
    - Roger G., undated (Box 3)
    - Wendy Rogers, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Romo and Gianell, undated (Box 3)
    - Bertram Ross and Deborah Zall, undated (Box 3)
    - Fred Ruegg, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Farouk Ruzimatov, undated (Box 3)
    - Carlota Santana Spanish Dance, undated (Box 3)
    - Yousry Sharif, 1996-1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Bill Talen, undated (Box 3)
    - Majorie Tallchief, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Michiyo Tanaka, undated (Box 3)
    - Gabrielle Taylor, 1980-1989, undated (Box 3)
    - Tasha Taylor, Lynn Shapiro, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Modesta Tellez and Coyote Feragosa, undated (Box 3)
    - Pat Terrio, undated (Box 3)
    - Twyla Tharp, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Ginger Thatcher, undated (Box 3)
    - Tom Thayer, undated (Box 3)
    - Rasta Thomas, undated (Box 3)
    - Richard Thomas, undated (Box 3)
    - Miles Thoroughgood, 1992-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Julie Tobiason, undated (Box 3)
    - Christopher Todd, undated (Box 3)
    - Diana Toni, undated (Box 3)
    - Patricia Torrero, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Christine Towers, undated (Box 3)
    - Joe Tremaine, 1987, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Robin Tribble, undated (Box 3)
    - Maura Umberto Trincia, undated (Box 3)
    - Yung Yung Tsuai, undated (Box 3)
    - Anthony Tudor, 1941, undated (Box 3)
    - Gayle Tufts, 1990, undated (Box 3)
    - Jacqueline Tuorto, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Roger Turner, undated (Box 3)
    - Donna Uchizono, 1993, undated (Box 3)
    - Unidentified photographs, undated (Box 3)